question_data = [

    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "Greenland is almost as big as Africa.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The first televised presidential debate was between Jimmy Carter and Gerald Ford.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The song &quot;Mystery Train&quot; was released by artist &quot;Little Junior&#039;s Blue Flames&quot; in 1953.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Sean Connery wasn&#039;t in &quot;Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull&quot; because he found retirement too enjoyable.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "Metallica collaborated with Rowan Atkinson&#039;s Mr Bean on a 1992 comic relief single.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "During pre-production of &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, Mario originally was meant to shoot bullets.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Franz Joseph I was the last emperor of Austria.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Space Station 13&quot;,  the station has a clown aboard it.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
